ourfamilywizard.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy | OurFamilyWizard

Skip to main content 

## Select your Language

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  
This Privacy Policy covers the OurFamilyWizard website's treatment of the personally identifiable information OurFamilyWizard collects on the OurFamilyWizard website site, when you use OurFamilyWizard website. This policy also covers the OurFamilyWizard website's treatment of any personally identifiable information that the OurFamilyWizard website's business partners share with OurFamilyWizard.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the OurFamilyWizard website does not own or control, or to people that the OurFamilyWizard website does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
The OurFamilyWizard website collects personally identifiable information when you register for an OurFamilyWizard website account, when you use certain OurFamilyWizard website products or services, when you visit OurFamilyWizard website pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes.

The OurFamilyWizard website is a web site designed to facilitate the management of your family’s life through features which include but are not limited to Calendaring and the management of information such as Addresses, Babysitters, Child Care Providers, Doctors, Activities, Emergency Contacts, Religious Information, Health Details, Immunizations, School Information, Vital Statistics, and Financial Information. While the information within these classifications may be required for the use of specific services or features of the OurFamilyWizard website web site, you are not required to use all of the services and features. Once you register with the OurFamilyWizard website and register for our services, you are not anonymous to us.

The OurFamilyWizard website also receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, OurFamilyWizard cookie information and the page you requested.

The OurFamilyWizard website uses information to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to provide electronic notification services for events in your calendar and to provide billing information to the OurFamilyWizard Accounts Receivable department.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
The OurFamilyWizard website will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

The OurFamilyWizard website will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when (1) we have to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, (2) we find that your actions on our web site violate the OurFamilyWizard website Terms of Use, (3) we have your consent to share the information, (4) we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested, or (5) we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of the OurFamilyWizard website to provide a product or service to you. Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary or in conformance with your request.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use the Platforms and also allows us to improve them. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our [Cookies Page](https://www.ourfamilywizard.com/cookies).

Other companies may also set and access cookies on your computer, for example, advertisers on the Platforms or providers of external services such as webs traffic analysis services.  We have no control over these third parties and their use of cookies is subject to their own privacy and cookie policies, not this one.  They do not have access to the data collected through the cookies we set.

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

The OurFamilyWizard website gives you the ability to edit your OurFamilyWizard website account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want OurFamilyWizard to contact you about special promotions and new products.

**Location**

OurFamilyWizard provides you with the ability to attach geographical identification tags (longitude/latitude) to entries.  This functionality is called geotagging.  Geotagging makes user content more organized and searchable.  Geotagged entries are created at the users discretion and geotags are ONLY generated when a user affirmatively adds them to an entry.  If you do not want to use our geotagging features, you may simply opt not to use them or turn off the location services located in your browser preferences or in your device settings.

**Security**  
Your OurFamilyWizard website Account Information is password protected for your privacy and security.

Because of the sensitivity of information stored on the OurFamilyWizard website, the OurFamilyWizard website uses not only industry standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions, but also uses Transparent Data Encryption and Redaction to protect data during storage and access inside of our database.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
The OurFamilyWizard website may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have suggestions, complete a feedback form, or send an email to:
